

Denver, CO · (720) 317-5614 · baileemanzer3@gmail.com · linkedin.com/in/bailee-manzer

Passionate social media specialist with a diversified background in marketing, content creation, and communication. A proactive leader, proven to show resilience amidst adversity while innovating communication concepts. I continue to grow my skillsets in the areas of social media and digital marketing, creating opportunities for impact.

CERTIFICATION, SKILLS & INTERESTS

- Google Ads Fundamentals Certification
- Google Ads Mobile Certification
- HubSpot Content Marketing Certification
- LinkedIn Social Media Marketing Tips Certification
- Proficent in Adobe InDesign, Photoshop, and Lightroom
- Efficient at copywriting, editing, and proofreading
- Skilled in Social Media Management, use of applications such as Buffer
- Apprentice in web development
- Portrait Photography
- Travel
- Skiing
- Hiking

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER, DU CODING BOOTCAMP | SEPTEMBER 2019 - PRESENT

- Designing and developing various web applications using technologies that include: Javascript, CSS, Node.js, Bootstrap, Firebase, MySQL, and React
- Collaborate with other developers on group projects workflow using Github

VISUAL CONTENT INTERN, INBOXLAB | OCTOBER 2019 - PRESENT

- Source images for multiple brands on multiple platforms using photography stock websites
- \bullet Oversee the use of photography on $\,$ multiple social media platforms
- Collaborate with editorial team to create new projects

MARKETING COORDINATOR, RE/MAX OF CHERRY CREEK | APRIL 2018 - PRESENT

- Managed social media platform, spearheading industry research and the use of Buffer and Facebook pages
- Initiated electronic and printed newsletter production using MailChimp and other applications
- \bullet Proposed innovative marketing avenues and managed administrative marketing initiatives

SOCIAL MEDIA, KELLER WILLIAMS REALTY | SEPTEMBER 2017 - DECEMBER 2017

- Integrated advanced social media strategy, increasing engaged audience by 25%
- Ensured maximum visibility and brand recognition through consistent maintenance of all social media platforms

EVENT MANAGER, BLACK CARD MANAGEMENT | JUNE 2017 - AUGUST 2017

- Recognized as a top national performer for revenue generation through in-store marketing campaigns
- Established vendor relationships and conducted promotional marketing events

EDUCATION